(Sheldon:)Ready?
(Bernadette:)You bet.
(Sheldon:)Your name is
(Sheldon:)Bernatrix.
(Sheldon:)You are a warrior queen.
(Sheldon:)You're strong,
beautiful and tall.
(Bernadette:)Oh. I like the idea
of being tall.
(Sheldon:)I think you're gonna like
a lot of things I have in store.
(Sheldon:)For example, in this world,
only the men get pregnant,
(Sheldon:)so your husband is home trying
not to pee when he laughs.
(Bernadette:)This is getting fun.
What's next?
(Sheldon:)You're parched and weary
from battle.
(Sheldon:)You stand in front of a tavern
that serves the coldest,
(Sheldon:)most delicious ale
in all the realm.
(Bernadette:)Oh, I haven't had
a drink in months.
(Sheldon:)What do you do?
(Bernadette:)I storm in, slam my sword down,
and say, “Barkeep, bring me
the strongest ale you have
(Bernadette:)and serve it in
the skull of a goblin!”
(Sheldon:)He wants to see I.D.
(Amy:)So, Claire, we've heard so many
wonderful things about you.
(Claire:)Really? Like what?